An electrifying experience - you won't believe your eyes!
Trilogy of Terror is a horror, thriller, tv movie film directed by Dan Curtis.
A horror anthology containing three stories: a female college professor is aggressively pursued by one of her students; a prudish brunette determines
that her free-spirited blonde sister is evil; and a woman's night turns upside down after she purchases an ancient Zuni fetish doll.
Julie / Millicent Larimore / Therese Larimore / Amelia, played by Karen Black.
Chad Foster, played by Robert Burton.
Thomas Amman, played by John Karlen.
Dr. Chester Ramsey, played by George Gaynes.
Eddie Nells, played by Jim Storm.
Anne Richards, played by Kathryn Reynolds.
Trilogy of Terror is a 1975 American made-for-television anthology
horror film directed by Dan Curtis and starring Karen Black.
It features three segments, each based on unrelated
short stories by Richard Matheson.
The first follows a college professor who seeks excitement with her students;
the second is about twin sisters who have a bizarre relationship.
These two segments were adapted by William F.
The third, adapted by Matheson himself, focuses on a woman
terrorized by a Zuni fetish doll in her apartment.
Black stars in all three segments, and plays dual roles in the second.
The film was first aired as an ABC Movie of the Week on March 4, 1975.
Black initially turned down the project, but reconsidered when her
then-husband, Robert Burton, was cast in the first segment "Julie".
A television film sequel titled Trilogy of Terror II, written and
also directed by Dan Curtis, was released in 1996.
The film explores themes of seduction, sister,
anthology, evil doll, horror anthology.
The tone is dark and intense.